<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Code Breaker</string>
    <string name="play1_button">Begin</string>
    <!--    <string name="play2_button">Two Player</string>-->
    <string name="master_pegs">Placeholder for generated codes to break</string>
    <string name="code_gen">Generate Code</string>
    <string name="game_board">Game board</string>
    <string name="tb1">red</string>
    <string name="tb2">pink</string>
    <string name="tb3">orange</string>
    <string name="tb4">yellow</string>
    <string name="tb5">green</string>
    <string name="tb6">blue</string>
    <string name="taskBarImg" />
    <string name="dropBox" />
    <string name="start_game">Start</string>
    <string name="rules">
        You are a Code Breaker. The goal is to crack the code consisting of a series of 4 colored pegs.
        \n \n Every time you guess, you get feedback that narrows down what the code is.
        \n \n Break the code in 10 guesses or less to win!
    </string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="row1">1</string>
    <string name="row2">2</string>
    <string name="row3">3</string>
    <string name="row4">4</string>
    <string name="row5">5</string>
    <string name="row6">6</string>
    <string name="row7">7</string>
    <string name="row8">8</string>
    <string name="row9">9</string>
    <string name="row10">10</string>
    <string name="demoDesc1">There are six colored pegs in your toolkit</string>
    <string name="demoDesc2">Scroll down to row 1 to start, then touch a peg and select a
        spot to put it (active spots are highlighted)</string>
    <string name="demoDesc3">A green checkmark appears once you fill in all four spots</string>
    <string name="demoDesc4">Tap the checkmark to submit your code. Each time you
        submit, your code is compared to the game\'s code and feedback is provided.</string>
    <string name="demoDesc5">The feedback appears on the left. RED indicates that one part of
        your code is the correct color and in the right place. WHITE indicates that one part
        of your code is the correct color but in the wrong place. Any slots without a RED or
        WHITE peg indicates that the color is not a part of the code. \n \n
        THERE IS NO ORDER TO THE FEEDBACK INDICATORS. There can also be duplicates,
        so don\'t count anything out too quickly!</string>
    <string name="demoDesc6">Once you break the code all four indicators will be RED. \n \n
        Don\'t worry if you don\'t get it in 10 tries, the code will appear at the top.
        You\'ll get the hang of it and become a Master Code Breaker! Tap the Start button
        when you feel comfortable with this task</string>
    <string name="demoImg">Demo image</string>
</resources>
